Do you know any famous Chinese stories, Li Ming?
李明  你知道一些有名的中国故事吗
Yes! I know many Chinese stories.
是的  我知道很多中国故事
Would like to hear one?
你想听一个吗
Yes! Yes! Tell us a story!
好  好  给我们讲个故事
Okay! I'm going to tell the story of a farmer and a rabbit.
好的  我给你们讲一个农民和兔子的故事
Long long ago, there was a farmer.
很久以前  有一个农民
He worked hard all the time.
他一直非常努力地劳作
One day, as he was working, a rabbit came out of the grass.
有一天  在他劳作的时候  一只兔子从草丛中跑了出来
The rabbit saw the farmer and it was scared.
兔子看见农民  非常害怕
It started to run.
兔子开始跑开
It ran very fast and hit its head on a tree.
它跑的飞快  头撞到一颗树上了
The rabbit died.
兔子撞死了
The farmer took the rabbit home.
农民把兔子带回家
He enjoyed a wonderful dinner.
他享用了一顿美妙的晚餐
From then on, he stopped working.
从那时起  他不再劳作了
Every day, he sat under the tree and waited for another rabbit.
每天  他就坐在树下等兔子
He waited and waited, but no rabbits came.
他等啊等  可是没有等到兔子
And all his crops died.
他的庄稼都死了